Email: anblaziak@gmail.com

ANNA BŁAZIAK

Full Stack Web Developer

Portfolio: https://aniablaziak.github.io/annablaziak-portfolio/

GitHub: https://github.com/aniablaziak

PROFILE

Full Stack JavaScript Web Developer experienced with working in Agile teams. Enthusiastic learner with excellent communication skills and a great eye for detail. Passionate about great user experience, creative problem solving and clean, readable code.

Technical Proficiencies: HTML, CSS, JavaScript (ES6), Node.js, Express, React, PostgreSQL, Handlebars.js, Sass, Jest, Travis CI, Figma, Heroku, Git & GitHub

EXPERIENCE

Software Development Student, Founders & Coders

MAR 2019 - JUN 2019, LONDON, UK

- Participated in an 18-week, full stack web development course with an emphasis on peer-led learning and **pair programming**
- Gained practical experience of working on projects in Agile teams
- Built full stack projects in collaborations with charities and NGOs with the use of **design thinking**, **user research** and **user testing**
- Hosted and mentored meetups for prospect future course students

Areas of learning: JavaScript (ES6), Node.js, Express, PostgreSQL, Semantic HTML, REST APIs, Sass, React, BEM, Test Driven Development, Continuous Integration services

Project Management Intern, Creative Translation

SEP 2018 - DEC 2018

Project Management Intern at a translation agency specialising in marketing translation, working with brands such as Airbnb, PayPal, Norwegian Airlines, to name a few. My experience working as a Project Manager in the translation industry taught me excellent time management skills, creative problem solving, managing working to tight deadlines and maintaining an impeccable eye for detail. It also strengthened my communication skills and empathetic approach to the product audience.

PROJECTS

Dish

Community meal sharing app created for co-workers who want to share homemade lunches. The app allows the users to create and browse available communities, as well as browse, post and claim available lunch listings.

Tech Stack: JavaScript, Sass, PostgreSQL, Handlebars.js, Express, Jest, Travis CI, Heroku

<u>Live Version</u>: https://community-dish.herokuapp.com/ GitHub Repo: https://community-dish.herokuapp.com/

Train Departures App

An app showing real-time train departure times and line statuses for London Underground train stations. Built with the TfL API.

Tech Stack: JavaScript, CSS, HTML, Node.js, Travis CI, Heroku Live Version: https://train-departures-app.herokuapp.com/
GitHub Repo: https://github.com/aniablaziak/week5-trains

EDUCATION

BA (Hons) Translation

SEP 2016 – JUN 2018 London Metropolitan University, United Kingdom BA English Studies (specialising in translation) OCT 2014 – JUN 2016 Adam Mickiewicz University, Poland

ADDITIONAL INFO

Here are some of tech conferences and meetups I have attended recently: Half Stack Conference 2018, ffconf 2018, // TODO Conf 2018
Front-end London, // TODO, Codebar, JSMonthly, CSS London